https://www.draytonhall.org/privacy-policy/

Condé Nast Traveler's Best Place to See in South Carolina.
Drayton Hall's main house, galleries, and landscape are open to the public weekly Wednesday through Sunday. The gate will accept no cash transactions.
To receive Drayton Hall’s newsletters and offers
sign up for emails here.
Visit
Admission
Group Tours
Private Guided Tours
Getting Here
COVID-19 Precautions FAQ’s
FAQs
The Estate
Scope of the Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy applies to the Website that is owned and operated by the Drayton Hall Preservation Trust (DHPT), a historic site of the National Trust for Historic Preservation in the United States. This Privacy Policy states the DHPT’s policy with regard to the personal identifiable information you provide.
The Drayton Hall Preservation Trust is committed to honoring the privacy preferences of members of the public that visit our Website. Our intention through this Website is to supply information that will help people learn about and experience Drayton Hall in fulfillment of our mission to preserve, educate and inspire. In the course of providing these online services, information may be exchanged between the DHPT, servers, online users and their browsers. In order to access certain materials or services on the Website, you may be asked to provide your name, address, phone number and/or other information. It is your decision to provide this information. We will only use this information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Please be advised that you may opt-out of receiving certain information from the DHPT as provided herein. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Website.
Personal Information Collected
PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED
The Drayton Hall Preservation Trust has a strong commitment to internet privacy.  We provide choices to the consumer in deciding when and how to provide different categories of “personally identifiable information” (e.g., data that may be used to identify, contact or locate a person such as name, physical address, e-mail address and phone number and information you provide to help customize your web experience).  In general, when you visit our Website and access information, we do not require you to register or provide personal identifiable information to us. However, there are occasions when we will ask for additional information.  For example, you may be required to register your name and e-mail address or other necessary information in order to enter future member-only areas of the Website. You may also be required to register your name and e-mail address and provide other information if you wish to receive e-newsletters or reply to surveys, contests, or other promotions.  It is your choice to provide such information, and you may opt-out from receiving any of this type of information in the future.
Personally identifiable information, such as your name, physical address, e-mail address, phone number and credit card information will be collected if you wish to become a member of the Drayton Hall Preservation Trust, make purchases online, or make online donations.  Please be advised that we will never share your credit card information.  Nor will we ever share your email address or other personal identifiable information provided unless otherwise authorized by you or as stated in this Privacy Policy.
INTERNET PROTOCOL AND COOKIES
We may keep track of your interactions with our Websites and our services to offer a more personalized experience through your Internet Protocol address or through the use of “Cookies” and web analytics services.
An Internet Protocol (IP) address is associated with the portal through which you enter the internet, like your internet service provider (ISP).  Standing alone, your IP address is not personally identifiable.  At times, we use IP addresses to collect information regarding the frequency with which our visitors visit various parts of our Website.  We may also combine this information with personally identifiable information, e.g., your name and address that you have provided to us and/or with other information that is publicly available or that we receive from other reputable sources in order to make our Website and communications more targeted to your interests.
“Cookies” are small files sent from a web server to your computer through your browser program that permit the computer to help customize your experience with our Website. The Drayton Hall Preservation Trust uses cookies to measure visitation to our Website, including repeat visitors and to perform certain functions such as order processing, registrations, and advertising.  Cookies may be used to store some history about the parts of our Website that you have visited to help you navigate our Website more easily or to alert you to related pages on our Website that may interest you.  The DHPT does not use cookies to obtain information about other websites that you may have visited.  The DHPT may also use web analytics services and conversion tracking, which use cookies and other means to collect and analyze data.  These services, however, do not collect personal identifiable information.  For more information about cookies, visit www.cookiecentral.com.
WEBPAGE SHARING AND E-CARDS
If a user elects to share pages from our Website with friends, colleagues, or on social media sites or send e-Cards, we ask for the recipient’s name and e-mail address.  The DHPT will automatically send the recipient a one-time message inviting them to visit a website.  The DHPT uses the recipient’s information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time e-mail, and the recipient information is not retained.
PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION CONTAINED IN USER CONTENT
Some sections of our Website may allow users to post or transmit messages, comments, screen names, computer files, and other materials.  We encourage your thoughts, stories, photos, but be advised that any content you submit to the Website will not be returned to you and may be used by the Drayton Hall Preservation Trust in any manner we see fit, including reprinting it in full or in modified version on our Website or elsewhere, or using elements of it on our Website.  You will not be entitled to any remuneration for any use of your content by the DHPT.
You are solely responsible for the contents of your transmission through our Website.  The DHPT is not obligated to monitor such transmissions, and therefore cannot be responsible for any personally identifiable information or other information that may be contained in such transmissions.  You agree not to transmit through the Website any unlawful, harassing, libelous, abusive, threatening, or harmful material of any kind or nature.
Please review the Drayton Hall Preservation Trust’s Terms of Use for more information regarding user content posted to the Website.
Use of Information and Privacy Choices
USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
If you provide the DHPT with your personal identifiable information, we will not share that information with other organizations, unless you have otherwise authorized us to do so or as stated in this Privacy Policy.
If you provide your personal identifiable information on a public forum (e.g. a blog) the DHPT is not responsible for monitoring these transmissions and cannot be responsible for any personally identifiable information contained in such transmissions.  Please review the DHPT’s Terms of Use for more information.  If you wish to be removed from one of our e-mail lists or from receiving information from the DHPT, you may opt-out at any time.
LINKS TO THIRD PARTY WEBSITES
We provide many links to third party websites existing outside of the DHPT. Since we do not control the content or functionality of these websites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on those third party websites. Any link from www.draytonhall.org to a third party website does not denote an affiliation with the website or an endorsement of its viewpoint(s) or mission(s).  Please review the DHPT’s Terms of Use for more information.
CO-BRANDED PARTNERS
From time to time, the Drayton Hall Preservation Trust may offer certain promotions, programs or activities on our Website that are co-sponsored or co-branded by non-profit and/or for-profit partners, such as purchasing products or services offered by our partners, or electing to participate in advocacy campaigns, contests, sweepstakes, games, or other programs sponsored in whole or in part by our partners, which will be subject to their own terms of use.  At the time of engagement, you will be offered an opportunity to choose to authorize the DHPT to share your information with our partners so you may receive information from the partners.  We do not control the privacy practices or terms of use of our co-branded partners; therefore, you should review their privacy practices before you choose to access their products or services.  You are entitled to opt-out from receiving any resulting information from the DHPT as set forth in this Privacy Policy at any time [include link to opt-out].  However, if at a later date, you decide to opt-out of receiving information from our partners, you will need to contact the partners directly.
LICENSEES
We may share your personally identifiable information (e.g. name and address) with third parties that offer products or services under or in association with brand names of the DHPT. A licensee is one whose products or services are offered to you with our name.  These licensees are restricted by contract to use your information solely for purposes of marketing or promotional materials related to DHPT products or services.  You are entitled to opt-out from receiving this information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.  If you choose to access purchases through one of our licensees, they may in some cases collect your personal identifiable information subject to their own privacy policies.  We do not control the privacy practices of our licensees; therefore, you should review their privacy practices before you choose to access their products or services, and you will need to contact the licensees directly to opt-out of receiving information from them.
THIRD PARTY ADVERTISING
We may use third party advertising companies to service ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to the Website in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.
OTHER DISCLOSURES
The Drayton Hall Preservation Trust will share personal identifiable information with third parties if we have a good-faith belief that disclosing the information is reasonably necessary to:
Meet applicable law, regulation, legal process, or enforceable governmental request;
Enforce the DHPT’s Terms of Use;
Detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; and/or
Protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of the DHPT as required or permitted by law.
Security of Your Credit Card Information
All information provided to the Drayton Hall Preservation Trust is transmitted using SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption.  SSL is a proven coding system that lets your browser automatically encrypt, or scramble, data before you send it to us.  We also protect account information by placing it on secure portions of our Website that are only accessible by certain qualified employees of the DHPT.  Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure.  While we strive to protect your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of such information.
If you do not wish to use our online payment services for ticket and merchandise sales and memberships, payment may be made by contacting our main number during regular business hours M-F , 9:00am to 5:00pm EST, at (843) 769-2600. An operator will direct your call.
The Drayton Hall Preservation Trust website includes links to online transactions for tickets, merchandise sales, and memberships that are operated by a third party company.  You should review the credit card security information and the privacy policies of those third party companies before making a purchase.
Compliance with Federal Laws
CHILDREN’S PRIVACY POLICY
The Website covered by this Privacy Policy does not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under the age of 13.  The Website is not directed to, nor do they have knowledge of, visitors less than 13 years of age. We are committed to protecting children’s privacy, and we will monitor our Website and their users to make sure that their privacy is protected. If we discover that a person under the age of 13 has provided us with any personal identifiable information, we will delete that information from our systems.  We are unable to reply to information requests from children under the age of 13, if so identified.  A parent or guardian must initiate the requests from children under the age of 13 on their behalf. If we begin marketing to children on-line and we are aware that those children are under the age of 13, the Drayton Hall Preservation Trust will take steps to fully comply with the Children’s Advertising Review Unit (CARU) and the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA). To learn more about both of these programs, see www.coppa.org.
SPAM
The Drayton Hall Preservation Trust complies fully with the Controlling the Assault on Non-Solicited Pornography and Marketing Act of 2003 (CAN-SPAM Act).  To this end, the DHPT:
ALWAYS provides recipients of e-mail marketing and e-newsletters a clear mechanism to opt-out of receiving information in the future and honors any such requests promptly.
ALWAYS provides accurate header and subject line information prior to sending any e-mails.  The DHPT commits to sending only e-mails with specific subject lines and a clear delineation from whom the e-mail was sent.
ALWAYS provides the DHPT’s physical address within the body of all of our e-mail messages.
Questions; Opt-Out
The Drayton Hall Preservation Trust welcomes comments or questions on this Privacy Policy.  We are dedicated to protecting your personal identifiable information and will make every reasonable effort to keep that information secure.  If you have any questions or wish to opt out, please contact us via email, phone or mail at:
Constituent Services Department
Drayton Hall Preservation Trust
3380 Ashley River Road
Charleston, SC 29414
pmarion@draytonhall.org
(843) 769-2604
Opt-out requests should include “Opt-Out” in the e-mail or letter subject line.
Any information you provide to us is covered by this Privacy Policy.
UPDATING YOUR INFORMATION
You can help the Drayton Hall Preservation Trust ensure the accuracy of your information.  If you have any changes to your physical address, title, e-mail address, name, or phone number, please submit an address change request to the Constituent Services Department via the contact information shown above.
Changes in this Privacy Policy
We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time.  Any material changes in the way we collect, use, and/or share your personally identifiable information will be posted on-line.  You are bound by such revisions and should therefore visit the page to review the current terms from time to time.  Your continued use of the Website constitutes an affirmative acknowledgement by you of the terms and modifications and your agreement to abide and be bound by the terms as modified.
Contact Us
(843) 769-2600
info@draytonhall.org
3380 Ashley River Road
Charleston, SC 29414
Get Directions
Hours
Drayton Hall's main house and landscape are open to the public Wednesdays - Sundays from 9 am to 3:30 pm (gate closes at 2:30 pm). Closed on Monday and Tuesday. The gate will accept no cash transactions.
Mon to Sat
OPEN Wednesday, Thursday, Friday, Saturday., and Sunday. CLOSED Mon. Tues.
Sun
Open
Drayton Hall is open weekly Wednesday through Sunday. Closed on Monday and Tuesday. *Entrance gate closes at 2:30 pm, site closes at 3:30 pm.*
